dipali patel

Anaheim, CA 92801 dipaliforever89@gmail.com

DIPALI PATEL (714)-553-5100 dipaliforever89@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Phlebotomy

Highly skilled career professional with more than 6 years practical experience in hospital, home health, and primary care environments.

Skillful and precise in performing venipuncture and capillary punctures; collecting, preparing and storing blood samples; and verifying medical records.

Possess an outstanding patient-relations skills and ability to alleviate patient anxieties Comprehensive understanding of compliance and safety

CREDENTIALS

Phlebotomist Tech 1 - CPT 121890

SKILLS

Computer-literate and Proficient user of Microsoft Office applications.

Lightly skilled on QuickBooks and Sage MAS90.

Medical terminology savvy.

Ability to Make Decisions and Solve Problems.

Good Interpersonal Skills

Dynamic, Innovative and Self-motivated.

EXPERIENCE

kaiser Permanente - Laboratory assistant II 2014- Present

Verify and print lab orders to obtain blood specimens for inpatient and outpatient. Pre analytical specimen processing.

Quest Diagnostics - Site Lead/Float/Certified Phlebotomist/ receptionist 2007- 2014

Westminster, CA.

Perform aseptic venipuncture procedures to obtain blood samples for analysis in order to obtain data, which may be used in diagnosis, monitoring and treatment of disease.

Prioritize workload according to urgency; coordinate with team members to meet the operational service needs.

Prepared, processed, and stored patient specimens and samples according to organization's procedures using standard techniques and equipment.

Performed laboratory computer operation.

Maintain records for the laboratory supplies and inventories.

Maintained health and sanitation standards in the laboratory.

Using proper procedures and standards that are used for positive patient identification.

Maintain the strictest confidentiality; adheres to all HIPPA guidelines /regulations

Hoag Hospital Newport Beach - Certified Phlebotomist 2009-2010 Newport Beach, CA.

Responsible for accurate and timely collection and processing of specimens in the sections assigned.

Delivered blood samples to various departments as required.

Prepared and organized of patient specimens for testing.

Conferring with patients to obtain information for laboratory records.

EDUCATION

University Of Phoenix - Present 4 classes to completion Bachelor of Science in Health Care Administration Allied Training Phlebotomy Certification Vidyanagar High School High School Diploma

WORK EXPERIENCE

Phlebotomist

quest diagnostics - Westminster, CA - August 2007 to Present

EDUCATION

bachelor in science of health care management in health care

university of Phoenix - La Palma, CA 2008 to 2014

SKILLS

Dedicated hard working employee with a strong work ethic. Highly motivated and self starter. Compassionate person who enjoys helping people. Committed to superior customer service while preserving customer confidentially. Punctual and dependable. Work well under pressure and enjoy a fast pace environment. Eager to learn new skills, A desire to complete education necessary for career growth, take on challenges, a detailed and organized person. Able to multi-task effectively, strong team player, trustworthy, ethical. Computer Savvy, Medical terminology savvy, good organization, communication, and interpersonal skills, Capable of handling multiple priorities in a high volume setting.

CERTIFICATIONS/LICENSES

Phlebotomist Tech 1 - CPT 121890

April 2007 to Present